I went to the UPS. I gave him the thing,
he puts in my phone number, he said,
"Hey,
is this your correct address?" And I
said, "Yes." He said, "Oh, let me see
your ID." I gave him my ID, he said, "Is
this your correct address?"
And I said, "I haven't moved, but that
is still the correct address."
You know, and I wanted to say I wanted
to like get mad, but then I remember he
was Gen Z and he would cry.
>> [laughter]
>> Sadly,
the dumbing down of America
has worked.
Cuz I get asked more ridiculous stupid
questions like not too long ago I moved
to Las Vegas. I live in Vegas now. And
the first thing people ask, "Wow, you
live in Vegas? Is it hot?"
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah.
They're like, "Oh, don't worry, it's a
dry heat." Really? So is an open flame.
>> [laughter]
>> I I NEEDED TO BUY LIKE mothballs for the
closet, right? So I go to the grocery
store and there's a guy, he's stocking
the shelves or whatever. I said, "Say,
man, where are the mothballs at?" And he
looked right at me and he said,
"How do you spell moth?"
And I thought about it for a minute and
I said,
"How do YOU MISSPELL MOTH?"
>> [laughter]
>> I'M MORE CONCERNED WITH what you might
come up with. HOW DO YOU
>> [laughter]
>> IT'S JUST IT'S THINGS THAT DON'T MAKE
sense And And the reason I say it's a
dumbing down cuz everything is now it's
set up for you being dumb. You know, my
car has a warning, like when you shut
the car off, it it lights up, "Did you
check the back seat?"
For people like Are that many people
forgetting people
in the back seat that the car has to
actually check with me?
You know, cuz see, I'm from a different
time. When I was a kid, there was no way
that they would forget a kid in the back
seat because my dad was yelling at us
the entire time.
We were YOU BETTER BE QUIET BACK THERE.
DON'T MAKE ME I'LL PULL this car OVER.
SHUT UP BACK THERE. There was no way he
was going to forget.
And the other thing back in those days,
whatever happened, it was the kids'
fault.
It was always our fault. My dad, he
would have threatened us not to die in
the heat while he left us in the car.
I'm going IN THAT STORE. WHEN I COME
BACK, YOU better be alive back there.
I dare you to die from this heat, you
know?
Me and my brother be looking at each
other like, "You going to die?" "I ain't
going to die, man. I ain't getting in no
trouble."
>> [laughter]
>> Gen Z, God bless them.
I don't mean to pick on them. They're
not dumb. I don't think they're dumb. I
just think they could be a little lazy.
They don't put a little effort into it,
right? Like I went to the UPS. And like
everywhere else, they have everything
off of your phone number, right? them
the phone number, it tells your name,
address, your whole account. So, I was
shipping some stuff. I got notarized
paper. I got work to do, you know? So, I
give him the thing. He puts in my phone
number. He said, "Hey,
is this your correct address?"
And I said, "Yes."
So, he did the package and that. And
then I said, "Well, I need to get this
notarized." He said, "Oh, let me see
your ID." I give him my ID. He said, "Is
this your correct address?"
And I said, "I haven't moved."
Like I understand it's been 3 minutes.
But that is still the correct address.
You know, and I wanted to say I wanted
to like get mad, but then I remember
he's Gen Z and he would cry.
>> [laughter]
>> So, I couldn't like actually say like
what what is wrong with you, you know? I
had had to be gentle. But sometimes they
really make me mad. When Gen Z behind
the counter really makes me mad, you
know what I do? I give them cash.
I just hand them like a $20 bill and I'm
like, "Now you got some work to do."
>> [laughter]
>> I actually had one they actually asked
me like, "What What is that?" And I was
like, "That's government crypto."
>> [laughter]
>> And I see some young people up front and
they're like, "Yeah, man, but you old."
That's right, I am.
And you know, here's the thing, cuz I
again, I I'm all for young people, good
for you. If anytime any old people ever
give you a hard time, you know what you
do? Just get up and run away without
warming up.
I hate when they do that. They
They're like, "Oh, I'm in a hurry." and
they just run and I'm like, "Wow.
Look at that. I
I get stereotyped. Like the number one
biggest stereotype I get is, "Man, do
you play pro football?" Like, "Yes, I'm
the oldest man in the NFL."
I've been in the league. I remember the
leather helmets. Let me tell you
something, man.
That plastic revolutionized the game.
You know why the football one bothers
me? Because I didn't know I could have
played football.
Right? My 20s, I had a job. I didn't
know I could have played football. I
grew up in New York City. We didn't have
football. We didn't have grass.
There's no football teams in New York
City, you know, not high school level. I
didn't know I could have just went to
the NFL like, "Hey,
I'm here to play football."
And they'd be like, "Have you ever
played football?" "No."
"Well, who told you you COULD PLAY
FOOTBALL?" SMALL WHITE PEOPLE.
>> [laughter]
>> THEY THINK THEY SEEM TO THINK I'D BE A
master at your little game, huh?
>> [laughter]
>> Stereotypes. Now, I'm looking for a car,
this dude said, "Man, I get you a great
deal on a Cadillac Escalade."
>> [laughter]
>> I'm like, "Well, what are you trying to
say, man?
Last thing I need is an Escalade. I look
enough like security.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't need to be rolling up in a
Cadillac Escalade, right? Soon as I pull
up, people think it's the Uber.
Now I got random people jumping in my
car.
Right? Next thing you know, bridal party
jumps in. I'm going to jail for
kidnapping six young white women.
>> [laughter]
>> My dog gets stereotyped.
I have a Great Dane. I love my dog. My
dog is a giant dog, you know? Always
hear the same thing. First they say,
"Wow, is that a horse?" I'm like, "Have
you ever seen a horse?
>> [laughter]
>> Way bigger than the dog, right? You need
to get out more."
>> [laughter]
>> And then the really dumb one they always
ask us, "How much does he poop?"
And I look at him and be like, "Well,
you know, he weighs about 165. You look
about 180. How much you dropping a day?
You two want to get into a little
contest?
Sure, we can find somebody to judge. I
don't
The one stereotype I will tell you
applies to me,
I don't hike.
Black people don't hike.
>> [laughter]
>> White people are like, "Oh, we're going
to go on a hike." Black people are like,
"Have fun."
>> [laughter]
>> I'LL GO FOR A WALK.
I ain't going for a hike. You know, I
don't understand like people want to go
out into the woods in the nature and go
hiking,
then they get killed by some animal and
they're shocked.
I saw a thing on TV. It was like, "How
to survive in bear country." I was like,
"DON'T GO."
>> [laughter]
>> I MEAN, IF THEY TOLD YOU IT'S bear
country, I'mma leave that to the bears.
They're not coming to my neighborhood.
Why am I in there? You understand?
>> [laughter]
>> I watch people do the dumbest things
around nature. The smartphone has made
people complete idiots.
Now, I'm watching this guy.
He was hiking. And he was like video you
had his phone. He's recording. There's a
bear less than 10 ft behind him.
And he's walking like, "The bear seems
to be calm.
I'm going to remain calm. He's right
behind me as you can see and well, I
have pepper spray." And I'm thinking the
bear is walking behind him like, "This
going to be the easiest meal I ever had.
This one's not even smart enough to run.
Oh, look. He's got pepper. WE HAVE
SPICES."
>> [laughter]
>> WHAT PEOPLE GET THEIR PHONE AND get
around animals, they lose their minds.
There's a a thing on Instagram. It's
called tourons of Yellowstone.
Touron is a combination of the words
tourist and
>> [laughter]
>> Because it's people who want to take
selfies with animals. They show people
want to take a selfie with a bison. Do
you understand how big a bison is? A
bison's like 7 ft tall, weighs 2,000 lb.
Basically, it's a van
with horns.
Right? And they're like, "I'm going to
go take a selfie." And me and everyone
in the comments are like, "COME ON,
BISON."
SO ARE YOU A BISON.
>> [laughter]
>> AND BISON ARE LAZY ANIMALS. So they
never really go bison, you know? But
every now and then
>> [laughter]
>> every now and then you get one.